<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="105">
    <author>Ozz</author>
    <version>1.0.0.5</version>
    <iconFilename>icon_RedTape.dds</iconFilename>
    <title>
        <en>Red Tape</en>
        <de>Papierkram</de>
        <fr>Paperasserie</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Red Tape

A mod that adds depth to the game by introducing Policies, Schemes and Tax.

Policies include animal welfare and environmental regulations that, if not followed, can result in fines or other penalties. 
Schemes offer opportunities for additional income or benefits but may come with their own set of requirements.
Tax adds a layer of financial management, requiring players to budget for regular tax payments based on their farm's income and activities.

Your performance in complying with Policies can impact the quality of rewards from Schemes and even offer tax benefits.

See the help menu in game for more information.

- GitHub:
https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_RedTape

Changelog:

1.0.0.5:
- Adds a workaround to address an issue in the Realistic Weather which causes an issue in this mod when spraying.

1.0.0.4:
- Safe guard added to prevent salt spreading scheme showing up multiple times at once.
- Rework of manure policy. The report will be incorrect initially, but in a way that it is more lenient until all the data is tracked.
- Rework of animal spacing policy. Age is now taken into account, e.g. a 2 month old cow requires less space than a 24 month old cow. Points will no longer be deducted during a month that produces a warning only.
- Clarify 14m buffer zone in spray violation policy description.

1.0.0.3:

- Fix a multiplayer only issue when spraying fertiliser
- Skip pigs and horses for the animal productivity policy.
- Brazilian translation added, thanks to MuhWalker.
- Russian translation added, thanks to Martin.

1.0.0.2:
- Fixed an issue where seeders that fertilised caused harmless errors in the log.
]]>
        </en>
        <de><![CDATA[Papierkram

Diese Mod erweitert das Spiel um Richtlinien, Programme und Steuern.

Richtlinien umfassen Tierschutz- und Umweltauflagen, deren Nichteinhaltung zu Bußgeldern oder anderen Strafen führen kann. Programme bieten Möglichkeiten für zusätzliches Einkommen oder Vorteile, sind aber mit eigenen Bedingungen verbunden. Steuern führen zu einer komplexeren Finanzplanung, da Spieler regelmäßige Steuerzahlungen basierend auf den Einnahmen und Aktivitäten ihres Betriebs einplanen müssen.

Die Einhaltung der Richtlinien beeinflusst die Qualität der Belohnungen aus Programmen und kann sogar Steuervorteile gewähren.

Weitere Informationen finden Sie im Hilfemenü des Spiels.

- GitHub:
https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_RedTape

Änderungsliste:

1.0.0.5:
- Fügt eine Umgehungslösung hinzu, um ein Problem im Realistic Weather zu beheben, das beim Sprühen in dieser Mod zu einem Problem führt.

1.0.0.4:
- Eine Sicherheitsvorkehrung wurde hinzugefügt, um zu verhindern, dass das Streusalzprogramm mehrfach gleichzeitig angezeigt wird.
- Die Güllerichtlinie wurde überarbeitet. Der Bericht wird zunächst fehlerhaft sein, jedoch so, dass er bis zur vollständigen Datenerfassung weniger streng ausfällt.
- Die Richtlinie zur Tierhaltung wurde überarbeitet. Das Alter wird nun berücksichtigt; beispielsweise benötigt eine zwei Monate alte Kuh weniger Platz als eine 24 Monate alte. In Monaten, in denen lediglich eine Warnung ausgegeben wird, werden keine Punkte mehr abgezogen.
- Klarstellung der 14-m-Pufferzone in der Beschreibung der Sprühverletzungsrichtlinie.

1.0.0.3:

- Problem beim Düngen im Mehrspielermodus behoben
- Schweine und Pferde bei der Tierproduktivitätspolitik überspringen
- Brasilianische Übersetzung hinzugefügt, vielen Dank an MuhWalker
- Russische Übersetzung hinzugefügt, vielen Dank an Martin

1.0.0.2:
- Es wurde ein Problem behoben, bei dem Sämaschinen, die Dünger ausbrachten, harmlose Fehler im Protokoll verursachten.
]]>
        </de>
        <fr><![CDATA[Paperasserie

Ce mod enrichit le jeu en introduisant des politiques, des programmes et des impôts.

Les politiques concernent le bien-être animal et la réglementation environnementale. Leur non-respect peut entraîner des amendes ou d'autres sanctions.

Les programmes offrent des opportunités de revenus ou d'avantages supplémentaires, mais peuvent être soumis à certaines conditions.

Les impôts ajoutent une dimension de gestion financière, obligeant les joueurs à prévoir un budget pour les paiements d'impôts réguliers en fonction des revenus et des activités de leur ferme.

Votre respect des politiques peut influencer la qualité des récompenses des programmes et même vous octroyer des avantages fiscaux.

Consultez le menu d'aide du jeu pour plus d'informations.

- GitHub:
https://github.com/sprkem/FS25_RedTape

Journal des modifications:

1.0.0.5:
- Ajoute une solution de contournement pour résoudre un problème dans le module Realistic Weather qui provoque un dysfonctionnement dans ce mod lors de la pulvérisation.

1.0.0.4:
- Un dispositif de sécurité a été ajouté pour éviter que le programme d'épandage de sel ne s'affiche plusieurs fois simultanément.
- Refonte de la politique relative au fumier. Le rapport sera initialement erroné, mais plus indulgent jusqu'à ce que toutes les données soient collectées.
- Refonte de la politique d'espacement des animaux. L'âge est désormais pris en compte: par exemple, une vache de 2 mois nécessite moins d'espace qu'une vache de 24 mois. Aucun point ne sera déduit durant un mois ayant généré uniquement un avertissement.
- Clarification de la zone tampon de 14 m dans la description de la politique de violation de pulvérisation.

1.0.0.3:

- Correction d'un problème lié au mode multijoueur lors de l'épandage d'engrais.
- Exclusion des porcs et des chevaux du calcul de la productivité animale.
- Ajout de la traduction brésilienne, grâce à MuhWalker.
- Ajout de la traduction russe, grâce à Martin.

1.0.0.2:
- Correction d'un problème où les semoirs qui fertilisaient provoquaient des erreurs sans conséquence dans le journal.
]]>
        </fr>
    </description>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/InitialClientStateEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/NewTaxLineItemEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/NewTaxStatementEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/PolicyActivatedEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/PolicyClearWarningsEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/PolicyFineEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/PolicyPointsEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/PolicyReportEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/PolicyWarningEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/PolicyWatchToggleEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/SchemeActivatedEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/SchemeEndedEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/SchemeNoLongerAvailableEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/SchemePayoutEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/SchemeReportEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/SchemeSelectedEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/SchemeWatchToggleEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/TaxRateBenefitEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/events/TaxStatementPaidEvent.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/BaleWrapperExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/FarmExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/FSBaseMissionExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/I18NExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/MissionManagerExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/PlaceableHusbandryAnimalsExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/PlaceableHusbandryExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/SaltSpreaderExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/SnowSystemExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/SprayerExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/extensions/TreePlantManagerExtension.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/gatherers/FarmGatherer.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/gatherers/FarmlandGatherer.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/gui/tableRenderers/ActivePoliciesRenderer.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/gui/tableRenderers/SchemesRenderer.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/gui/tableRenderers/EventLogRenderer.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/gui/tableRenderers/ReportRenderer.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/gui/tableRenderers/TaxNotesRenderer.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/instances/EventLogItem.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/instances/Policy.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/instances/Scheme.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/instances/TaxLineItem.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/instances/TaxStatement.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/system/EventLog.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/system/InfoGatherer.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/system/PolicyList.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/system/PolicySystem.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/system/SchemeList.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/system/SchemeSystem.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/system/TaxSystem.lua"/>
        <sourceFile filename="src/RedTape.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n" />
    <helpLines>
        <category title="$l10n_rt_help_title_red_tape">
            <page title="$l10n_rt_help_title_intro" iconSliceId="helpline.icon_shop">
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_intro_intro"/>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_intro_intro_2"/>
                </paragraph>
            </page>
            <page title="$l10n_rt_help_title_policies" iconSliceId="helpline.animals_general">
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_policies_intro"/>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_policies_intro_2"/>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_policies_intro_3"/>
                </paragraph>
            </page>
            <page title="$l10n_rt_help_title_schemes" iconSliceId="helpline.forestry_treeTypes">
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_schemes_intro"/>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_schemes_intro_2"/>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_schemes_intro_3"/>
                </paragraph>
            </page>
            <page title="$l10n_rt_help_title_tax" iconSliceId="helpline.firstSteps_shop">
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_tax_intro"/>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_tax_intro_2"/>
                </paragraph>
                <paragraph>
                    <text text="$l10n_rt_help_tax_intro_3"/>
                </paragraph>
            </page>
        </category>
    </helpLines>
</modDesc>